Leon:
Hi Shannon – how are you settling into your new flat?
Shannon:
Really well, thanks.
Leon:
You look like you’re going shopping.
Shannon:
Yes, I am.
My cousins are coming to stay for a couple of days,
and I have to cook for them.
Leon:
Well, there are plenty of places to buy food in Kite Place – it’s
the area by the harbour.
Shannon:
Oh, OK, I’ll find that on the map.
Thanks.
Leon:
What sort of food do you need to get?
Shannon:
Well, neither of them eats meat but they both like fish.
Leon:
Well, there’s a really good fish market there.
Shannon:
Oh great – where is it exactly?
Leon:
It’s at the far end of Kite Place,
so you have to go over the bridge and then it’s on the
right.
Shannon:
OK – is it open all day?
Leon:
It doesn’t close until four,
but I’d recommend going earlier than that – it does run out of some
things.
Shannon:
Oh, I don’t want that to happen.
Leon:
As long as you get there by 3.30, you should be fine.
It’s only 11 now,
so plenty of time.
Shannon:
Right.
Leon:
Do you need to buy vegetables too?
Shannon:
I do,
and I want to avoid all the plastic packaging in the supermarket!
Leon:
Well, there’s a really nice organic shop there.
Now what’s it called .
.
it’s the name of a flower.
I know, it’s ‘Rose’.
Shannon:
That’s a nice name.
Leon:
Yeah – it sells vegetables and quite a lot of other stuff.
Shannon:
And where’s that?
Leon:
Well, as you reach the market, you’ll see a big grey building on your
left
Leon:
I think it used to be a warehouse.
Anyway, now it’s a restaurant upstairs,
but the ground floor has two shops either side of the entrance
and it’s the one on the left.
Shannon:
That’s easy enough.
Leon:
You can’t miss it – there’s also a big sign on the pavement
so you can look for that.
Shannon:
Fine!
I guess if I need anything else, I’ll have to go to the
supermarket.
Leon:
Yeah – you should be able to get everything you need,
but there’s a minibus that goes to the supermarket if you need it.
It’s purple and the number is 289.
Shannon:
Thanks,
that’s great.
Leon:
So what do you need to get at the fish market?
The salmon is always very good and the shellfish.
Shannon:
I’m going to make a curry, I think,
and I need about 12 prawns for that.
Leon:
They’ll have plenty of those.
Shannon:
OK.
Leon:
Have you ever tried samphire?
Shannon:
No – what’s that?
Leon:
It’s a type of seaweed.
I just ask for a handful and you fry it in butter.
It’s delicious!
Shannon:
Oh, I might try that – how do you spell it?
Leon:
It’s S-A-M-P-H-I-R-E.
Shannon:
Great – it’s always good to try something different.
Leon:
Yeah.
Shannon:
I’ll see what beans they have in the organic shop
and I think I’ll get something for dessert there.
Leon:
How about a mango?
Shannon:
I’m not sure – they’re not always ripe.
I’d prefer a melon – it’s bigger too.
Leon:
Good idea.
The owner also sells a lot of spices there that you can put in
a curry,
and things like coconut.
Shannon:
Oh,
that’s very helpful.
I’ll have a look.
Leon:
No problem.
Shannon:
I know bread doesn’t really go with curry but I always like to have
some in case.
Leon:
As I said – all the bread is home-made and there’s lots of variety.
I like the brown bread myself.
Shannon:
Mm, sounds good.
Leon:
They sell other things there too.
Shannon:
Like cakes?
I love chocolate cake.
Leon:
Well – not that,
but they have a whole range of tarts and the best are the strawberry
ones.
Shannon:
Perfect – hopefully I won’t even have to go to the supermarket!